{
	"id": 1,
	"title": "Lesson 1",
	"description": "Use basic phrases, talk about food and drink",
	"content": [
		{
			"type": "fillBlank",
			"question": ["Mo", "madam"],
			"answer": "ene",
			"options": ["ene", "tifi", "bwar"],
			"translation": "I am a woman"
		},
		{
			"type": "fillBlank",
			"question": ["Li p", "dilé"],
			"answer": "bwar",
			"options": ["manz", "dipain", "bwar"],
			"translation": "He is drinking milk"
		},
		{
			"type": "fillBlank",
			"question": ["Zot p", "diri"],
			"answer": "manz",
			"options": ["misier", "bwar", "manz"],
			"translation": "They are eating rice"
		},
		{
			"type": "match",
			"options": {
				"water": "delo",
				"milk": "dilé",
				"rice": "diri",
				"boy": "garson"
			}
		},
		{
			"type": "match",
			"options": {
				"man": "misier",
				"woman": "madam",
				"bread": "dipain",
				"girl": "tifi"
			}
		},
		{
			"type": "multipleChoice",
			"question": "How do you say 'bread'?",
			"answer": "dipain",
			"options": ["tifi", "diri", "dipain"]
		},
		{
			"type": "multipleChoice",
			"question": "How do you say 'water'?",
			"answer": "delo",
			"options": ["delo", "diri", "madam"]
		},
		{
			"type": "multipleChoice",
			"question": "How do you say 'girl'?",
			"answer": "tifi",
			"options": ["tifi", "diri", "misier"]
		},
		{
			"type": "multipleChoice",
			"question": "How do you say 'a'?",
			"answer": "ene",
			"options": ["madam", "mo", "ene"]
		},
		{
			"type": "multipleChoice",
			"question": "How do you say 'you'?",
			"answer": "to",
			"options": ["to", "mo", "tifi"]
		},
		{
			"type": "translate",
			"question": "He is a man",
			"answer": "Li ene misier",
			"options": ["misier", "ene", "pa", "garson", "Li"]
		},
		{
			"type": "translate",
			"question": "She is a girl",
			"answer": "Li ene tifi",
			"options": ["tifi", "ene", "manz", "dipain", "Li"]
		},
		{
			"type": "translate",
			"question": "To ene garson",
			"answer": "You are a boy",
			"options": ["boy", "You", "a", "are", "girl"]
		},
		{
			"type": "translate",
			"question": "To p manz dipain",
			"answer": "You are eating bread",
			"options": ["eating", "are", "a", "You", "bread"]
		},
		{
			"type": "translate",
			"question": "He is eating bread",
			"answer": "Li p manz dipain",
			"options": ["p", "bwar", "Li", "manz", "dipain"]
		}
	]
}
